Seaman Jacobs Scripts
Seaman Jacobs Scripts
1946-1992
Jacobs, Seaman.
7 linear ft.
Collection contains scripts written by Seaman Jacobs for television comedy shows. Extent of coverage varies.
1650729
Biographical History
Seaman Jacobs was a comedy writer for such productions as "The Joey Bishop Show," "Here’s Lucy," and several Bob Hope television specials.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Seaman Jacobs Scripts contains scripts for television shows for which Jacobs was the author. Television shows are primarily comedy shows or situation comedies; shows represented include The Red Skelton Show, Bob Hope, Here's Lucy, No Time For Sergeants, Bachelor Father, F-Troop, The Real McCoy's, The Jimmy Stewart Show, and How to Marry a Millionaire.
Arrangement of the Collection
Scripts are arranged in no particular order by title of show, and within that by episode air date. The catalog number for each episode is given in parentheses ( ).
Related Material
has a number of television-related collections. Please refer to for a complete listing
Subject and Genre Headings
Radio, television, film; Popular culture; Television scripts.; Television comedies -- United States.; Variety shows (Television programs) -- United States.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Seaman Jacobs.
Inventory
- Scripts
  - The Red Skelton Show
    - There's One Thing Money Won't Buy, & Someday We'll Find Out #902, 8/25/69 (Box 1)
    - Pop, The Astronaut #903, 8/29/69 (Box 1)
    - Willie Lump Lump's Birthday #904, 8/26/69 (Box 1)
    - Babysitter And The Farmer's Son, Indian Princess Sketch #905, 9/16/69 (Box 1)
    - Autograph Hounds, Hominy And True Grits #906, 10/28/69 (Box 1)
    - The Emergency Case, Tribute To W.C. Fields #907, 11/4/69 (Box 1)
    - Alaska #908, 11/11/69 (Box 1)
    - Singing Waiters, HillBilly Songwriters #909, 11/18/69 (Box 1)
    - There's One Thing Money Won't Buy, And Someday We'll Find Out What #910, 11/25/69 (Box 1)
    - It Is Better To Have Loved And Lost, Much Better #911, 12/2/69 (Box 1)
    - He Wanted To Be A Square Shooter, But He Found That His Barrel Was #912, 12/9/69 (Box 1)
    - The Son Of Oliver Twist Or Junior Is Just A Little Dickens #913, 12/16/69 (Box 1)
    - Crime Doesn't Pay But Its Tax Free #914, 12/30/69 (Box 1)
    - You Can Take The Boy Out Of The Country, If You Promise Not To Bring #915, 1/6/70 (Box 1)
    - If Marriages Are Made In Heaven, Why Do They Call It Heaven #916, 1/13/70 (Box 1)
    - Blood Is Thicker Than Water And Harder To Shave With #917, 3/10/70 (Box 1)
    - There's No Business Like Show Business, When There Is No Business #918, 1/27/70 (Box 1)
    - Charity Begins At Home, But Nowadays Who Can Afford A Home #919, 1/27/70 (Box 1)
    - Is This The Way To Ruin An Airline, Plastic Surgeon #920, 2/10/70 (Box 1)
    - When East Meets West, You've Sure Got A Skinny Country #921, 2/2/70 (Box 1)
    - People Who Like People Are Cannibals #922, 2/9/70 (Box 1)
    - The Three Musketeers Ride Again, Those Ding-Dong Daddies #923, 2/24/70 (Box 1)
    - Bill Bailey Must Have Been Married That's Why He Never Came Home #924, 3/3/70 (Box 1)
    - He Died With His Boots One Cause He Had Cold Feet To Start #925, 3/17/70 (Box 1)
    - San Fernando's Spy School or How To Make A Possible Mission Impossible #926, 3/24/70 (Box 1)
    - Be It Ever So Crumbled, There Is No Place Like Home #927, 3/31/70 (Box 1)
    - Stone Walls Do Not A Prison Make - So They Added Bars #928, 4/7/70 (Box 1)
  - Bob Hope
    - Bob Hope's Funny Valentine Special, 2/11/81 (Box 1)
    - Bob Hope's All - Star Comedy Look At The New Season, 9/27/81 (Box 1)
    - Bob Hope Presents A Celebration With Stars Of Comedy, 10/22/81 (Box 1)
    - Bob Hope's Women I Love - Beautiful But Funny, 2/28/82 (Box 2)
    - Happy Birthday Bob, Kennedy Center For The Performing Arts, 5/23/83 (Box 2)
    - Bob Hope Lampoons Television, 1985, 2/24/85 (Box 2)
    - Bob Hope Buys NBC, 9/17/85 (Box 2)
    - Bob Hope With His Easter Bunnies & Other Friends, 4/19/87 (Box 2)
    - Bob Hope Salutes The U.S.A.F. 40th Anniversary, 5/25/87 (Box 2)
    - NBC Investigates Bob Hope #1 87/88 Season, 9/17/1987 (Box 2)
    - Stand By For Him - The Hope Funny News Network, 9/8/88 (Box 2)
    - Bob Hope's 1988 Christmas Show from Miami, Florida, 12/19/88 (Box 2)
    - Bob Hope's Superbowl Party, 1/5/89 (Box 2)
    - Bob Hope's 1989 Easter Special From Crystal Place Resort, 3/25/89 (Box 2)
    - Ooh-La-La... It's Bob Hope's Birthday Spectacular From Paris, 5/4/89 (Box 2)
    - Bob Hope's 1989 Christmas Show From Waikoloa, Hawaii, 12/16/89 (Box 2)
    - Ole! It's Bob Hope's Spring Fling of Comedy And Music From, 4/9/90 (Box 2)
    - Bob Hope's USO Road To The Berlin Wall And Moscow, 5/19/90 (Box 2)
    - Bob Hope's Don't Shoot It's Only Me #1 90/91 Season, 9/15/1990 (Box 2)
    - Bob Hope's 1990 Christmas Show From Bermuda, 12/15/90 (Box 2)
    - Bob Hope's Christmas Cheer In Saudi Arabia #3 90/91 Season, 1/12/1991 (Box 2)
    - Bob Hope's Yellow Ribbon Party, 4/6/91 (Box 2)
    - Bob Hope & Friends.. .Making New Memories, 9/12/91 (Box 2)
    - Bob Hope's Cross-Country Christmas Special, 12/18/91 (Box 2)
    - Bob Hope And Other Young Comedians: The World Laughs, 3/14/92 (Box 2)
    - Bob Hope Lampoons Show Business - Bob's Comedy Revue Of #3 89/90 Season (Box 2)
  - George Burns
    - The George Burns One Man Show, 9/14/77 (Box 2)
    - George Burns 100th Birthday Party, 11/9/78 (Box 2)
    - George Burns In Nashville, 9/2/80 (Box 2)
    - George Burns Early, Early, Early Christmas Special, 6/17/81 (Box 3)
    - 80 Years In Show Business, 8/13/83 (Box 3)
  - Here's Lucy
    - A Date For Lucy, 7/29/68 (Box 3)
    - Guess Who Owes Lucy 3.50?, 9/3/68 (Box 3)
    - Lucy And Liberace, 10/6/69 (Box 3)
    - Lucy's Vacation, 6/10/70 (Box 3)
    - Lucy's House Guest, Harry, 9/10/70 (Box 3)
    - Lucy's Lucky Day, 6/9/71 (Box 3)
    - Lucy's Replacement, 8/31/71 (Box 3)
    - Lucy's Punctured Romance, 10/6/71 (Box 3)
    - Lucy And Her Prince Charming, 1/3/72 (Box 3)
    - Lucy And Her Prince Charming (copy 2), 10/22/71 (Box 3)
    - Kim's Singing Group Encounter, 2/22/72 (Box 3)
    - Lucy, The Other Woman, 3/9/72 (Box 3)
    - A Home Is Not An Office, 3/16/72 (Box 3)
    - Lucy And The Group Encounter, 5/26/72 (Box 3)
    - My Fair Buzzi, 7/13/72 (Box 3)
    - Lucy And Her Genuine Twimby, 7/28/72 (Box 3)
    - Lucy Goes To Prison, 8/14/72 (Box 3)
    - Lucy's Replacement (Copy 2), 8/16/72 (Box 3)
    - The Bow-Wow Boutique, 6/25/73 (Box 3)
    - Lucy's Tenant, 8/13/73 (Box 3)
    - Harry Catches Gold Fever, 9/14/73 (Box 3)
    - Lucy, The Sheriff, 10/30/73 (Box 3)
    - Mary Jane's Boyfriend, 11/14/73 (Box 3)
  - The Lucy Show
    - Lucy Gets Mooney Fired, 4/3/67 (Box 3)
    - Lucy, The Starmaker, 5/15/67 (Box 3)
    - Lucy the Philanthropist, 8/14/67 (Box 3)
  - No Time For Sergeants
    - Bully For Ben, 5/10/64 (Box 3)
    - Blood Hounds Are Thicker Than Water, 5/19/64 (Box 3)
    - Blue's Wild Yonder, 5/21/64 (Box 3)
    - Will Gets A Right Hand Man, 5/22/64 (Box 3)
    - The Velvet Wiggle, 6/8/64 (Box 3)
    - Grampa's Airlift, 6/11/64 (Box 3)
    - Two Aces In A Hole, 6/25/1964 (Box 3)
    - Do Me A Favor And Don't Do Me Any, 6/26/64 (Box 3)
    - The Spirit Of Seventy-Five, 7/2/64 (Box 3)
    - Will Goes To Washington, 7/30/64 (Box 3)
    - The $100,000., 9/3/64 (Box 3)
    - The Farmer In The Deal, 9/21/64 (Box 3)
    - Oh Krupnick, My Krupnick, 10/1/64 (Box 3)
    - Two For The Show, 10/13/64 (Box 3)
    - Stockdale's Island, 10/22/64 (Box 3)
    - Stockdale's Millions, 11/3/64 (Box 3)
    - My Fair Andy, 11/12/64 (Box 3)
    - The Living End, 11/17/64 (Box 3)
    - Stockdale, General Nuisance, 11/24/64 (Box 3)
    - Too Many Stockdales, 11/30/64 (Box 3)
    - A Hatfold Of Muscles, 12/5/64 (Box 3)
    - Krupnick Strikes Again, 12/11/64 (Box 3)
    - It Shouldn't Happen To A Sergeant, 12/21/64 (Box 3)
    - The Case Of The Revolving Witness, 1/7/65 (Box 3)
    - Stockdale Of The Stockcade, 1/22/65 (Box 3)
    - Will's Misfortune Cookie, 1/28/65 (Box 3)
    - The Day Blue Blew, 2/11/65 (Box 3)
    - Whortleberry Roots For Everybody, 2/17/65 (Box 3)
    - Andy Meets His Match, 2/22/65 (Box 3)
    - Target Stockdale, 3/2/65 (Box 3)
    - The Sergeant's Kimono, 11/14/65 (Box 3)
  - The Ed Wynn Show
    - A Prospectus (Box 4)
    - [no title] #1, 9/22/49 (Box 4)
    - [no title] #3, 10/6/49 (Box 4)
    - [no title] #4, 10/13/49 (Box 4)
    - [no title] #5, 10/20/49 (Box 4)
    - [no title] #6, 10/27/49 (Box 4)
    - [no title] #19 (Box 4)
    - [no title] #29, 4/8/50 (Box 4)
    - [no title] #32 (Box 4)
    - The Scholarship #4349, 7/30/58 (Box 4)
    - Younger than Autumn #4404, 8/20/58 (Box 4)
    - The Parking Ticket #4431, 9/26/58 (Box 4)
    - New York Adventure #4446, 10/9/58 (Box 4)
    - The New Boy In Town #4455, 10/16/58 (Box 4)
    - Friendship Club #4486, 11/14/58 (Box 4)
    - Aunt Lydia Comes to Town #4419 (Box 4)
  - F-Troop
    - Background On Western Television Series (Box 4)
    - Story Outline For The Pilot Script, 8/3/64 (Box 4)
    - Scourge Of the West, 9/11/64 (Box 4)
    - Scourge Of The West, 12/21/64 (Box 4)
    - Here Comes The Tribe, 6/22/65 (Box 4)
    - Iron Horse Go Home, 6/30/65 (Box 4)
    - Dirge Of The Scourge, 7/8/65 (Box 4)
    - Honest Injun, 7/23/65 (Box 4)
    - Reunion For O'Rourke, 12/22/65 (Box 4)
    - A Fort's Best Friend Is Not A Mother, 3/1/66 (Box 4)
    - The Day That The Injuns One, 3/14/66 (Box 4)
  - The Mother's in Law
    - The Career Girls #5892-4, 5/4/67 (Box 4)
    - How Do You Moonlight A Meatball, 7/25/67 (Box 4)
    - Didn't You Used To Be Ossie Snick, 5/20/68 (Box 4)
    - Love Thy Neighbor-If You Can't Make Him Move, 5/30/68 (Box 4)
  - Bachelor Father
    - Peter Meets His Match #12403, 5/25/59 (Box 4)
    - The Case Against Gisele #12409, 5/22/59 (Box 4)
    - Bentley And The Brainy Beauty #12410, 9/28/59 (Box 4)
    - The Very Friendly Witness #12428, 1/8/60 (Box 4)
    - Fortune Cookie Caper #12431, 1/6/60 (Box 4)
    - Bentley, The Model Citizen #12439, 12/7/59 (Box 4)
    - Kelly Learns To Drive #12455, 7/11/60 (Box 4)
    - Bentley And The Big Board #12460, 8/31/60 (Box 4)
    - It Happens In November #12461, 8/30/60 (Box 4)
    - Bentley's Barbecue #12471, 9/1/60 (Box 4)
    - Bentley And The Wood Pecker #12476, 10/20/60 (Box 4)
    - Peter Plays Cupid #12481, 2/6/61 (Box 4)
    - Peter's China Doll #12485, 1/16/61 (Box 4)
    - Bentley And The Nature Girl #12488, 2/13/61 (Box 4)
    - Bentley Slays A Dragon #12489, 3/20/61 (Box 4)
    - A Favor For Bentley #12492, 4/4/61 (Box 4)
    - A Party For Peter #15608, 6/1/61 (Box 4)
    - Blossom Comes To Visit #15611, 12/8/61 (Box 4)
    - Here's Tenting Tonight #15616, 8/21/61 (Box 4)
    - Peter's Punctured Wedding #15621, 7/5/61 (Box 4)
    - Will Succes Spoil Jasper #15629, 8/1/61 (Box 4)
    - Gold In Them Hills #15633, 8/23/61 (Box 4)
    - Bentley Takes It Easy #15635, 3/22/62 (Box 4)
    - Blossom Time At The Greggs #15641, 3/12/62 (Box 4)
    - Blossom Time At The Garden #15641, 3/12/62; Missing, 5/2007
    - A Visit From The Bergens #15643, 1/17/62 (Box 4)
    - Marry Thy Neighbor #15643, 3/30/62 (Box 4)
  - The Joey Bishop Show
    - Five Brides For Joey #7, 9/12/61 (Box 4)
    - Charity Begins At Home #10, 10/9/61 (Box 4)
    - The Taming Of the Brat #15, 11/14/61 (Box 4)
    - Must The Show Go On #28, 3/1/62 (Box 4)
  - The Andy Griffith Show
    - Mayberry Elects A Sheriff, 2/5/63 (Box 4)
    - Goodbye, Dolly #25G (214), 12/14/66 (Box 4)
    - Howard, The Comedien #26G (215), 1/5/67 (Box 4)
    - Goober The Executive 2H (221), 6/22/67 (Box 4)
    - The Tape Recorder 9H (228), 8/10/67 (Box 5)
    - Aunt Bee And The Lecturer 11H (230), 9/6/67 (Box 4)
    - Andy's Investment 12H (231), 9/14/67 (Box 4)
  - The Danny Thomas Show
    - Rusty's Birthday DT#19-J (300), 10/23/62 (Box 5)
    - Linda And The Ground Up DT#25-J (306) (Box 5)
    - The Antique Dealers, 11/7/63 (Box 5)
    - The Leprechan DT#23-K (336), 11/28/63 (Box 5)
  - Petticoat Junction
    - The Courtship of Floyd Smoot #6000-4, 6/8/63 (Box 5)
    - The Little Train Robbery #6000-6, 7/1/63 (Box 5)
    - The President Who Came To Dinner #6000-8, 7/31/63 (Box 5)
    - Is There A Doctor In The Roundhouse? #6000-9, 8/1/63 (Box 5)
  - The Tycoon
    - Baby Tycoon #3, 11/19/63 (Box 5)
    - No Place Like Home #7, 5/4/64 (Box 5)
    - Harvey Brinkerhoff, Who Needs You?, 5/13/64 (Box 5)
    - Toys In The Pentigon #12, 5/28/64 (Box 5)
    - A Dog's Life #13, 7/10/64 (Box 5)
    - Johnny On The Spot #26, 10/26/64 (Box 5)
  - Westinghouse Playhouse
    - A Tale Of Two Mothers #13806, 10/17/60 (Box 5)
    - Those Golden Days #13823, 1/13/61 (Box 5)
    - Narn Suits Dan #13828, 4/27/61 (Box 5)
  - Oh! Those Bells
    - Seal Of Approval #4502, 6/15/60 (Box 5)
    - The Unfriendly Friendship Club #4504 (Box 5)
    - The Camping Trip #4506 (Box 5)
    - Mexican Holiday #4511 (Box 5)
    - The Case Of The Light- Fingered Chimp, 11/18/60 (Box 5)
  - Two for the Road
    - A Screen Comedy By Si Rose and Seaman Jacobs (Box 5)
  - Min and Bill
    - A New Half Hour Comedy Series, 8/6/63 (Box 5)
  - Take Me to the Fair
    - The Richmond Productions #3, 4/10/62 (Box 5)
    - [no title], 5/15/1962 (Box 5)
    - [no title], 8/6/1962 (Box 5)
  - Mother is a Freshman
    - Alias Miss Abbott, 1/7/58 (Box 5)
  - Adven. Of the Ambassador's Daughter
    - [no title] (Box 5)
  - Miss Gulliver Travels
    - Format For A New Television Comedy Series (Box 5)
  - The Jean Arthur Show
    - My Client The Rooster #27608, 6/3/66 (Box 5)
    - Blackstone-Italian Style #27615, 8/2/66 (Box 5)
    - A Slight Case Of Music #27618, 9/19/66 (Box 5)
    - Will You Raise Your Right Paw #27619, 10/6/66 (Box 5)
  - The Donna Reed Show
    - Operation Deadbeat #4575, 3/18/59 (Box 5)
  - Different Strokes
    - The Spanking 103, 11/1/78 (Box 5)
    - The Relative #112, 2/2/79 (Box 5)
    - Room for One More #318, 2/27/81 (Box 5)
  - Castles By the Sea
    - Pilot Script Of A Comedy Adventure Series For Television (Box 5)
  - The Thin Man
    - A Funny Thing Happened On The Way To The Morgue Jul-07, 12/30/58 (Box 5)
    - Cherchez La Sexpot #1248, 2/3/59 (Box 5)
    - Sublease On Death #1293, 2/3/59 (Box 5)
  - My Favorite Martian
    - How To Be A Hero Without Really Trying, 4/19/63 (Box 5)
    - Do Me A Favor: Don't Do Me Any Favors, 5/9/63 (Box 5)
    - The Unsuitable Suitor, 6/12/63 (Box 5)
  - Holiday Lodge
    - Twinkle Twinkle Little Star #15208, 7/3/61 (Box 5)
    - Jewel Thieves Anonymous, 7/17/61 (Box 5)
  - The Eve Arden Show
    - The French View #2, 8/8/57 (Box 5)
    - The Montana Date #10, 8/13/57 (Box 5)
    - Liza And The Bombshell #9, 9/4/57 (Box 5)
    - Lize Hammond Enterprises #13, 9/24/57 (Box 5)
    - Safari #16, 10/29/57 (Box 5)
    - Liza's Reunion Dance #18, 11/18/57 (Box 5)
  - The Jimmy Stewart Show
    - A Hunch In Time #9, 8/12/71 (Box 6)
    - As The Escrow Flies #15, 9/2/71 (Box 6)
    - A Bone of Much Contention #24, 11/18/71 (Box 6)
  - Bringing up Buddy
    - Buddy Hires A Maid #14323, 1/23/61 (Box 6)
    - Buddy And The Amazon #14326, 3/7/61 (Box 6)
    - The Aunts Have A Baby #14329, 3/28/61 (Box 6)
    - Buddy And The Teenager #14335, 4/25/61 (Box 6)
  - Run Buddy Run
    - My Son The Killer #2725-0809, 6/14/66 (Box 6)
    - Killer Cassidy #2725-0811, 7/6/66 (Box 6)
    - A Bad Run At The Gopher Flats #2725-0812, 7/18/66 (Box 6)
  - The Jonny Morgan Show
    - [no title] #1, 7/9/46 (Box 6)
  - Oh, Brother!
    - [no title], 10/3/1979 (Box 6)
  - The Bob Cummings Show
    - One Of Our Rock n Rollers Is Missing, 6/9/61 (Box 6)
  - Club Oasis
    - [no title], 11/22/1957 (Box 6)
  - Maude
    - Poor Albert #415, 11/18/75 (Box 6)
  - Garviola, The Matador
    - [no title] #2730, 2/18/59 (Box 6)
  - The Dennis O'Keefe Show
    - What Happened To Thursday #9333, 3/24/60 (Box 6)
  - Alice
    - Oh, George Burns #1, 12/4/77 (Box 6)
  - The Real McCoy's
    - Cupid Wore A Tail, 7/10/62 (Box 6)
    - The Little Boy Blew, 8/2/62 (Box 6)
    - How Are You Gonna Keep 'em Down On The Farm After They've Seen San..., 8/9/62 (Box 6)
    - Uncle Rightly And The Musical Milker, 8/16/62 (Box 6)
    - Pepino's Inheritance, 8/23/62 (Box 6)
    - Up To Their Ears In Corn, 9/6/62 (Box 6)
    - The Other Side Of The Fence, 9/12/62 (Box 6)
    - Farmers And Adele #201, 10/8/62 (Box 6)
    - Aunt Win Arrives #212, 12/20/62 (Box 6)
    - Aunt Win Steps In #213, 12/27/62 (Box 6)
    - The Auction #223, 1/15/63 (Box 6)
  - How to Marry a Millionaire
    - Alias The Secretary #0000005-10, 10/1/57 (Box 6)
    - Loco Versus Wall Street #0000005-24, 3/10/58 (Box 6)
    - A Job For Jesse #0-000005-43, 5/7/58 (Box 6)
    - A Man For Mike #0000005-45, 5/19/58 (Box 6)
    - Cherchez La Roomate #15-01, 5/6/59 (Box 6)
    - The Three Stacked Stock Holders #0000015-05, 5/14/59 (Box 6)
    - The Seal That Came To DInner #15-11, 5/15/59 (Box 6)
    - Gwen's Secret #15-09, 5/15/59 (Box 6)
    - Loco The Teenager #15-12, 5/20/59 (Box 6)
  - Earn Your Vacation
    - [no title] #1, 5/23/54 (Box 6)
    - [no title] #2, 5/30/54 (Box 6)
    - [no title] #3, 6/6/54 (Box 6)
    - [no title] #4, 6/13/54 (Box 6)
    - [no title] #5, 6/20/54 (Box 6)
    - [no title] #6, 6/27/54 (Box 6)
    - [no title] #7, 7/4/54 (Box 6)
    - [no title] #8, 7/11/54 (Box 6)
    - [no title] #9, 7/18/54 (Box 6)
    - [no title] #10, 7/25/54 (Box 6)
    - [no title] #12, 8/8/54 (Box 6)
    - [no title] #13, 8/15/54 (Box 6)
    - [no title] #14, 8/22/54 (Box 6)
    - [no title] #15, 8/29/54 (Box 6)
    - [no title] #16, 9/5/54 (Box 6)
  - Dalton My Partner
    - Dial "D" For Dancing, 9/24/65 (Box 6)
  - Staten Island
    - A New Musical Comedy (Box 6)
  - The Addams Family
    - One Man's Dragon #7000-1, 7/21/64 (Box 6)
  - How To Live To Be 100 or More
    - [no title], 9/17/84 (Box 6)
    - Lose Me An Albatross By Milton Pascal (Box 6)
  - Lose Me An Albatross
    - By Milton Pascal (Box 6)
  - I Dream of Jeannie
    - Jeannie And The Great Bank Robbery 4293, 9/26/67 (Box 6)
  - Set-Up
    - By Milton Pascal (Box 6)
  - The Temperature's Rising
    - Do Do The Voo Doo To Me #184411, 8/29/72 (Box 6)
  - The Magic Mondo
    - The Surfing Contest #MM-101, 6/28/77 (Box 6)
  - The Gale Storm Show
    - Oh! Suzanna #LD-217 (Box 6)
  - Hank
    - The Trouble With Tina, 11/9/65 (Box 6)
    - His Highness, Count Gazzari, 11/26/65 (Box 6)
    - Operation Matriculation, 1/13/66 (Box 6)
  - My Three Sons
    - Almost The Sound Of Music #5272-126, 5/2/63 (Box 7)
    - Adventures In New York #5272-149, 7/18/63 (Box 7)
    - One Of Our Moose Is Missing #5272-158, 4/17/64 (Box 7)
  - The Dennis Day Show
    - The Saga of F.H. La Due #128 (Box 7)
    - It's Dubarry's #131 (Box 7)
    - Reunion With Volcano Lips #133 (Box 7)
    - Mumps The World #136 (Box 7)
  - The Johnny Morgan Show
    - [no title] 2, 7/18/46 (Box 7)
    - [no title] 3, 7/25/46 (Box 7)
    - [no title] 4, 8/1/46 (Box 7)
    - [no title] 5, 8/8/46 (Box 7)
  - Saks Fifth Avenue
    - A Synopsis Of A Story With Music (Box 7)
  - Enough to Go Around
    - [no title] (Box 7)
  - Love Has a Cold Nose
    - An Outline For A Motion Picture Comedy (Box 7)
  - Spittin' Image
    - Pilot Script For TV Comedy Series, 7/1/81 (Box 7)
  - My Husbands And I
    - Proposed TV Comedy Series (Box 7)
  - The Bill Dana Show
    - The Hot Dog Caper #25, 1/6/63 (Box 7)
  - The Betty White Show
    - Honesty #102, 2/7/58 (Box 7)
  - KM Crossovers
    - Miscellaneous Jokes (Box 7)
  - The New Phil Silvers Show
    - Harry, The Good Neighbor #S-22, 1/6/64 (Box 7)
  - Quigley Of the MP's
    - Pilot Script, 5/9/66 (Box 7)
  - Family Affair
    - Class Clown #2245-0194, 4/30/70 (Box 7)
  - One Happy Family
    - Mildred For President #12, 2/6/61 (Box 7)